<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UNL Bathrooms</string>
    <string name="title">UNL Bathrooms</string>
    <string name="find_bathrooms">Find Bathrooms!</string>
    <string name="unl_logo">UNL logo</string>
    <string name="avery_hall">Avery Hall</string>
    <string name="Burnett_hall">Burnett Hall</string>
    <string name="contribute_title">Request a Bathroom</string>
    <string name="contribute_button">Contribute</string>
    <string name="avery_description">On City Campus, Avery Hall is southeast of Memorial Stadium and home to the Math and Computer Science departments</string>
    <string name="under_construction">This page is currently under construction</string>
    <string name="avery_hall_basement">Avery Hall Basement</string>
    <string name="avery_hall_first">Avery Hall 1st Floor</string>
    <string name="avery_hall_second">Avery Hall 2nd Floor</string>
    <string name="avery_hall_third">Avery Hall 3rd Floor</string>
    <string name="contribute"><u>Click here if you would like to contribute and add a bathroom</u></string>
    <string name="burnett_hall_basement">Burnett Hall Basement</string>
    <string name="burnett_hall_first">Burnett Hall 1st Floor</string>
    <string name="burnett_hall_second">Burnett Hall 2nd Floor</string>
    <string name="burnett_hall_third">Burnett Hall 3rd Floor</string>
    <string name="floor_plan_description">Men\'s bathrooms will be denoted by an \"M\", followed by a number (Ex:M1). Women\'s bathrooms will be denoted by an \"W\", followed by a number (Ex:W1).</string>
    <string name="avery_mens_basement">The largest bathroom in Avery, this bathroom boasts seven stalls(two handicap), three urinals, and four sinks.
    In between classes this bathroom becomes very busy, causing it to be quite messy at times. What do I mean by messy? Sometimes you go into a stall and it looks like
    teenagers were TP-ing a house that wouldn\'t give them candy on Halloween. Because of the amount of traffic, this bathroom gets 3 stars in spite of it\'s large amount
    of amenities.</string>
    <string name="burnett_mens_basement">A typical bathroom in burnett hall, this bathroom boasts 4 stalls(1 handicap), 2 urinals, and 2 sinks.
    There is always free because no classroom in here. if you are unable to find avaliable space. it'd s good choice to go basement.there is also the most clean place in burnett hall</string>
    <string name="burnett_mens_first">A typical bathroom in burnett hall, this bathroom boasts 4 stalls(1 handicap), 2 urinals, and 2 sinks.
    There are lost of classroom in here so it is busy between class. but the cleaniness in here is very good.</string>
    <string name="burnett_mens_second">A typical bathroom in burnett hall, this bathroom boasts 4 stalls(1 handicap), 2 urinals, and 2 sinks.
    There are some classroom in here but not very much.It's is empty in most time and get better cleaniness than first floor.</string>
    <string name="burnett_mens_third">A typical bathroom in burnett hall, this bathroom boasts 4 stalls(1 handicap), 2 urinals, and 2 sinks.
    This bathroom is always empty unless come to lunch time.the cleaniness is also very good</string>
    <string name="avery_mens_first">On the busiest floor of Avery sits the smallest bathroom in the building. One urinal, one stall, and two sinks. If you try to use this
    bathroom in between classes, prepare to wait in line. If you\'re patient enough to wait in line, you will realize the pressure on your shoulders once it\'s your turn. You can
    feel the eyes on the back of your head, glaring at you to hurry up and finish. Expect no privacy in here. The only plus side of this bathroom is it is relatively clean for
    how much traffic it receives. This is because if someone makes a mess, it\'s easy to find the culprit. There is no way you can wash your hands and exit the bathroom without
    someone seeing what you\'ve done. You will be caught.</string>
    <string name="avery_mens_second">Avery\'s best kept secret. I was hesitant to write an honest review for this bathroom because of the increased activity that is bound to come.
        Two urinals, two stalls(one handicap), and three sinks are more than enough for this hidden gem. Due to the low amount of traffic, this bathroom is exceptionally clean. Come here
        for a relaxing experience, whether it\'s relieving yourself or simply sitting in a stall and enjoying a sandwich.
    </string>
    <string name="avery_mens_third">Two urinals, two stalls(one handicap), three sinks. Identical to the bathroom on the second floor but a little more traffic. Nothing special about this
    bathroom, but it will get the job done.</string>
    <string name="contribute_description">If you would like to have a bathroom added to the app, please include: \n
    - what building and floor the bathroom is in \n
    - a rating \n
    - a picture of the bathroom \n
    - a review </string>
    <string-array name="unl_buildings">
        <item>Avery Hall</item>
        <item>Burnett Hall</item>
        <item>Oldfather Hall</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="avery_floors">
        <item>Basement</item>
        <item>1st Floor</item>
        <item>2nd Floor</item>
        <item>3rd Floor</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="burnett_floors">
        <item>Basement</item>
        <item>1st Floor</item>
        <item>2nd Floor</item>
        <item>3rd Floor</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="avery_basement_bathrooms">
        <item>Women\'s 1</item>
        <item>Men\'s 1</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
